Abbas Zabier Mohammad

Email: abbas.zabier06@gmail.com | Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/abbaszabier/ | Github: github.com/abbaszabier

Website: abbaszabier.site | Phone (wa): +62 88211156895 | Address: Banjar City, West Java

Summary

I am a frontend web developer with a computer science background from IPB University. As a frontend web developer with less than one year experience, I have experience in website development and have done two internships with frontend developer roles. I am very interested in programming, especially in the frontend developer field. I can also work independently as well as with a team and am always looking to improve my skills through learning and personal projects.

Education

IPB University

Aug 2018 - March 2023

Fresh Graduate, Computer Science

Work Experiences

Frontend Developer Intern at DSITD IPB

Jan 2023 - March 2023

- Responsible for reengineering the SITI website using ASP .NET MVC and Bootstrap.
- Collaborated with the UI/UX design team and backend team to create optimal website.
- Deliver responsive and cross-browser friendly websites.

Frontend Developer Intern at DSITD IPB

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

- Responsible for developing specific features on the Digitani web project, namely Konsultani and Tanya Pakar using framework Laravel and Bootstrap.
- Collaborated with the UI/UX design team and backend team to create optimal features.
- Delivers features that are responsive and cross-browser friendly.
- Implemented progressive web apps (PWA) for the Konsultani and Tanya Pakar features.
- Conducted testing and fixed bugs on the Konsultani and Tanya Pakar features.

Skills

Hard Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, C#, React Js, Laravel, ASP .NET MVC, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, jQuery, Wordpress, Version Control/git.

Tools: Visual Studio/Visual Studi Code, XAMPP, SQL Server Management Studio

Languages: Indonesia (Native), English (Limited working proficiency)

Selected Projects

Website SITI IPB

• Tech stack: ASP .NET MVC, Bootstrap

Konsultani & Tanya Pakar on Web Digitani

• Tech stack: Laravel, Bootstrap, Workbox

Website UMKM Desa Mulyasari

• Tech stack: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap